





About me:

A confident and highly motivated person with proven experience in operating in the Marketing and Sales departments. With a friendly and approachable persona, I am able to elicit the needs of clients and adapt to new environments diligently.

WORK EXPERIENCE

11/01/2016 - 11/04/2016 - Baku, Azerbaijan

PR AND MARKETING ASSISTANT - PORT OF BAKU

- Managing and sharing content with users on social media sites such as Twitter and Facebook
- Researching, writing, and distributing press releases to targeted media.
- Participating in the PR and Marketing projects.
- Managing inquiries from media, individuals, and other organizations.

02/05/2016 - 02/07/2016 - Baku, Azerbaijan

MARKETING ASSISTANT – BARATTSON SCHOOL OF BUSINESS AND FINANCE

Creating and executing online promotion campaigns for the company.

- Managing the design and production of promotional materials, such as websites and brochures.
- Looking after the budget of the marketing department and making sure the budget spend is delivering a return on investment.
- Writing and delivering content and social media plans.
- Tracking the effectiveness of marketing campaigns and reporting findings to the executive team.

01/08/2017 - 24/10/2021 - Baku, Azerbaijan

SALES AND MARKETING MANAGER - AZERBAIJAN VACATION LLC

- Create and execute a strategic sales plan that expands customer base and extends global reach
- Responsible for creating new B2B leads for the travel company using various online channels such as Google and Linkedin.
- Creating new online tour packages and promoting them via Google Ads, Facebook, and Instagram.
- Communicating with B2B clients located in various countries and designing service products based on their requests
- Overseeing the execution of the sold services at the local level.
- Launching new online promotional offers for the low season.
- Researching and analyzing market trends

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

15/09/2012 – 31/05/2016 – Koroglu Rahimov strt 822/23, Baku, Azerbaijan **MARKETING –** Azerbaijan Tourism and Management University

www.atmu.edu.az

13/10/2013 – 31/05/2016 – Koroglu Rahimov strt 822/23, Baku, Azerbaijan, Am Campus Krems, Krems an der Donau, Austria, Krems, Austria

BACHELOR OF ARTS IN BUSINESS - IMC FH Krems University of Applied Sciences

https://www.fh-krems.ac.at

22/10/2021 - CURRENT - Zygmunta Cieplaka, Dąbrowa Górnicza, Poland

PROJECT MANAGEMENT – Akademia WSB Dąbrowa Górnicza (Note: All the lectures are only at the weekends)

https://wsb.edu.pl/

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): AZERBAIJANI

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	C2	C2	C1	C2	B2
TURKISH	C2	C2	C2	C2	C2
RUSSIAN	C1	B2	A2	A2	A2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

Microsoft Office | Microsoft Word | Microsoft Excel | Microsoft Powerpoint | Google Drive | Google Docs | Skype | Zoom | LinkedIn | Social Media | Power Point | Organizational and planning skills | Google - Google Adwords

DRIVING LICENCE

Driving Licence: B

ORGANISATIONAL SKILLS

Skills and Knowledge

- Successful working in a team environment as well as independently
- Excellent Communication Skills
- Delivering a high level of customer service
- Critical and Goal-Oriented Thinking
- Intermediate MS Office tools user
- Excellent Lead generator

IELTS CERTIFICATE

16/04/2021 - 16/04/2023

Overall Band Score 8

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1PXeJwSYZwPcjD_d_NRTiz45fN8o8JFKm/view?usp=sharing